深呼吸
Okay, I'm going to ask you to take a deep breath in.
呼气
And you can let it go.
再继续吸气吗
Should I do it again?
不用 一次就够了
No, one is good.
知道为什么生气吗 上个星期二
...upset about? Apparently last tuesday...
有个筹款人带的是棒棒糖蛋糕
...we had this fundraiser...
而我带的是纸杯蛋糕
...and I brought cupcakes,she brought cake pops.
她的意思好像是干吗跟我带一样的
And she's like,"That's too similar."
我说 哪里 纸杯蛋糕就是纸杯蛋糕
I'm like,"No, a cupcake is a cupcake.
棒棒糖蛋糕是有跟棍子插住的
A cake pop is cake with a stick in it."
辛西娅 你要挪一下
Cynthia? I'm going to ask you to scooch down the table now...
再翻下身
Mmm-hmm....and turn over, please.
我们都是成年人了 还在为蛋糕争个你死我活的
We are grown women and we're fighting about cake pops.
这也没什么好说的 不过问题是
You know I mean let's get over it already!But the real issue is...
她女儿艾丽西亚是个好孩子
...her daughter Alicia is a very nice girl,
虽然不聪明 可是我的女儿安娜
but not very smart, whereas my daughter Anna...
伊娃 你好啊 见到你真好
Hey, Eva.Nice to see you.
上来吧
Hey. Come on up.
-还好吗 -不错 -那就好
- How's everything? - Great. - Alright.
让一下
Excuse me.
Hey, Mom.
你去哪
Where are you going?
陪莎拉和威尔去个派对
To a party with Sarah and Will,
他们就不会无聊了
so they don't have to be alone.
你想去吗
You wanna come?
为什么
Why?
因为你快走了 我想陪你啊
Because you're leaving soon,and I want to be with you.
我很好 谢谢
I'm good, thanks.
-玩的开心 -谢谢 亲爱的
- Have fun. - Thanks, honey.
我们快疯了
She's driving us totally crazy.
东西永远不知道在哪
We can't find anything.
她都放在乱七八糟的地方
She puts things in the weirdest places.
我放在厨房的手镯
Like, if I leave my bracelet in the kitchen,
她就会帮我扔到柜子里去
she'll put it in a kitchen drawer!
你为什么不能狠点心呢
Why can't you just do it?
哪里没有 我炒了园丁 你这么说太不公平了
I always do it. I fired the gardener.It's not fair.
我想要炒了她 他不愿意
We want to fire her,and he won't do it.
对你来说轻而易举 干吗要求公平
It's not hard for you. Why does it have to be fair?
你觉得难为情你就去做
You should do it because it's hard for you.
别扯了
Oh, please.
莎拉 你是个成年人了 我看好你
Come on, Sarah. You're a grownup.You can fire a maid.
成熟对你来说
That's the definition of maturity?
就是炒了你那该死的仆人咯
Being able to fire your friggin' maid?
莎拉 这颜色怎么样
Sarah, is this color good on me?
很好 很配你
You look good. You look pretty.
很好看
That's good. That's a nice look.
话说谁举办的这个派对
Whose party is this, anyway?
他是个编辑 她是室内设计师 他们人缘很好
He's a book editor and she's an interior designer. They know everybody.
-也许有黄金单身汉哦 -做梦吧
- Maybe some single men are here. - No.
糟糕 有个病号
Oh, shit, I see a patient.
-你想干吗 -指给我看看
- Oh, what you gonna do? - Will you show me?
-别想了 -给我看看是哪个
- No way. - Will you show me which one is it.
-给我介绍介绍 -不 别看了
- Come on, introduce me. - Stop looking. No.
天啊 你太扫兴了
God, you're such a wet blanket.
我的客户在那 太巧了
Oh, look it! There's that lady from my gym. What is...
-再见 -拜拜
- Okay, bye. - Bye.
我忘了她名字
What is her name?
想起来了 希拉里
Oh, it's Hilary.
希拉里 你好啊
Hilary? Hilary!
伊娃 好啊
Eva! Hi.
你怎么会在这
It's so weird to see you here.
伊娃 她是玛丽安妮 玛丽安妮 她叫伊娃
Eva, this is Marianne. Marianne, Eva.
-你好 -你好吗 -很好 -很高兴见到你
- Hello - How are you? - I'm good. - Nice to meet you.
我也是
Nice to meet you.
伊娃的按摩技术太棒了
Eva is an incredible,incredible masseuse.
-太好了 -谢谢
- Wonderful. - Thank you very much.
我不行了 我得去找个厕所
Excuse me a second.I have, I have to find a bathroom.
她太唐突了
That was abrupt.
天啊 看看你的鞋子和衣服
Oh, my goodness! Look at those shoes and that outfit.
还有包包 简直绝配啊
You got the purse and everything? It looks so nice.
谢谢 我带你逛逛吧
Thank you. I should bring you everywhere.
-你的衣服也很好看啊 -谢谢
- I love your outfit, too. - Oh.
你是按摩师吗
So you're a masseuse?
是的
I am, yeah.
哦
Yeah?
你做什么的
And what is it you do?
我是个诗人
I'm a poet.
我也是啊(Poet也有空想家的意思)
Oh. And I'm a dreamer.
我说真的
No, really.
你真的是诗人啊
You're really a poet?
对啊
I am.
用来谋生吗
You do it for a living?
-是啊 -太不可思议了
- I do. - Wow!
你用来赚钱 我用来空想 你是个诗人 我懂了
You do, I don't. You're a poet, now I know it.
很好
Good one.
想要点子找我啊
Feel free to steal it.
能帮我拿着吗 谢谢
Can I give that to you? Thank you.
猜猜怎么了
Guess what?
-怎么了 -我搞到一个新客户
- What? - I think I just got a new client.
在哪
Yeah? Where?
那边
Ah, right there.
她看起来不错
She looks clean.
她很幽默风趣 品味不错
She's really nice and funny,she's got great taste.
很迷人
And very attractive.
你觉得这里的女人都很迷人吧
You probably think all the women here are attractive.
差不多
Pretty much.
帮我拿着 这里没一个能入我法眼的
Hold this. There's not one man at this party I'm attracted to.
威尔
Will.
詹森 你好
Hey! Jason! How you doing?
-这是艾伯特 -你好
- This is Albert. - Hi.
-你好 -你好
- How's it going? - How are you? Hi.
那么多白色灯泡点缀的派对太棒了
So, this is a nice party. Got all the nice white balls hanging down.
伊娃刚刚说这里没有
Eva was just telling me that there are
一个男人她看得上的
no men at the party she's attracted to.
好吧
Okay.
我不明白你干吗要说出来 但是
I don't know why you would make that announcement, but...
真的吗 以前没有过吗
Really? Is that unusual?
不 无意冒犯 实际上我一直这样认为
No, actually, it's not unusual. No offense.
不会 我也是这样觉得的
No, that's okay. There's no one here I'm attracted to, either.
人还挺多
Yeah, it's kind of an ugly crowd, really.
詹森 你有个小孩在读大学 对吗
Jason, you have a kid in college, right?
两个
Two. Yeah.
我的小孩秋天就去上大学了
I have one leaving in the fall.
我的也是
I do, too!
-舍不得啊 -我也是
- That's all I have. - Me, too.
你们应该让他们出去闯闯 这样对他们比较好
Come on. Your kids are supposed to go away. That's healthy.
不要 闭嘴
No. Shut up.
闭嘴吧
Yeah, shut up.
-没有人会有反应吗 -不会
- Do the guys get boners? - No.
-天啊 你还有完没完 -对啊
- Oh god. Haven't we been over this? - Yes.
一想到按摩我就紧张
I get so nervous with massages.
一直担心我会勃起
I'm always afraid that I'm going to get a boner.
-你会吗 -绝对啊
- You are? - Absolutely. Absolutely.
他们会挑逗你吗
Do they hit on you?
你让我恶心了
Okay, you're starting to depress me.
不 他们不会挑逗我 也不会勃起
No, they don't hit on me.They don't get boners, either.
只是有一个人从来不帮我提按摩椅
I do have one guy who has like a hundred stairs going up to his house...
可是上去他家有一百多个台阶
...and he never helps me carry my massage table.
你有叫他吗
Did you ever ask him to?
-她不需要啊 -不 我不需要
- She shouldn't have to! - No, I shouldn't have to!
再见 谢谢 爱你们
Bye, guys. Thank you. Love you.
宝贝 再见
Bye, honey!
伊娃 再见 谢谢你载我一程
Bye, Eva! Thanks for the ride.
克洛伊 不用谢
You're welcome, Chloe.
麦迪·普赖斯
Oh, Maddy Price!
别乱扔垃圾
You littered, honey.
你说什么
What did you say?
我说把垃圾捡起来 这是美国
I said, pick up your trash.You're not British.
多管闲事
What a bitch.
-进来吧 -谢谢
- Come on in. - Thank you.
-很高兴见到你 -我也是
- Nice to see you. - Nice to see you too.
你可以把按摩椅放这
You can just put your table down right there.
介意把你鞋子脱了吗
Would you mind taking your shoes off?
不会啊
Oh no. Not at all.
-谢谢 还有袜子也要脱掉 -真的吗 -很好 -看来要脱
- Thank you. And your socks, too. - Oh,sure? -Great. -Absolutely.
你喝冰茶吗
Do you want some iced tea?
可以 谢谢
That sounds good. Thank you.
你打电话过来太好了
I'm so happy you called.
因为大多数人只是出于礼貌拿了名片
You know. Most people usually just take my card to be polite.
我可不会乱接名片喔
Well, I'm not polite.
天啊 这也太好了吧
Oh, my, isn't this nice!
哇
Wow.
谢谢
Thank you!
别客气 随便看看
Just make yourself at home, look around.
我去换衣服 马上就好
I'm gonna go change.I will be back in minute.
天哪 这也太美了吧 我能住进来吗
Oh god. Everything is so pretty! Can I live here?
茶也很好喝
That tea's kind of fabulous, too.
我的男朋友太严肃了
I'm dating this guy.He has no sense of humor.
真是大煞风景啊
That can be a dealbreaker.
我不知道该怎么办 他真的很贴心
I don't know what to do.Because he's very very sweet.
那很好啊
Sweet can be good.
你可以和其他人讲笑话嘛
Maybe you can find someone else to tell you jokes.
你结婚了吗
Are you married?
离婚十年了
Divorced. Ten years.
你们还是朋友吗
Are you still friends?
不是
No, not really.
我们除了拥有一个女儿之外
We share a daughter,but other than that...
难以置信的是我和他根本没共同话题
...it's hard to believe that I ever had a laugh with that man...
小孩也是神不知鬼不觉地怀上了
You know... let alone create a child.
我了解 我们也是没一点共同之处
I know what you mean about your ex.We had zero in common.
我都不知道和他聊的是什么
I don't know how I ever had a real conversation with him.
很疯狂 对吧
It's crazy, right?
不介意的话我会马上再喊你过来的
I'd like to call you pretty soon if it's all right.
我的右肩还是很痛
My right shoulder is still very tight.
晚上用冰缚着
You should ice it tonight.
多喝水
And drink plenty of water.
注意保持水分
It's important to stay hydrated.
我会注意的 你要点雪维菜吗 我非常喜欢
Of course. Hey, do you want some chervil? I'm drowning in it.
可以
Sure.
把刚摘的给你
I'll just give you what I've cut.
没有东西给你装啊
I don't have anything to put it in, but...
-我拿着就行 谢谢 -好吧 -很好
- Oh, that's ideal. Thank you. -Alright. -Lovely.
谢谢
Thank you.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
雪维菜是什么鬼东西 她说她迷上了
What the hell is chervil? She said she was drowning in it.
一种药草
It's an herb.
-什么东西 -药草
- A what? - An herb.
我认识你也不是一天两天了
How long have you known me?
我不懂你在说什么
I can't understand a damn thing you say.
天哪
Oh, my God.
每件物品都是那么完美 我想要啊
Everything in that house was gorgeous.I wanted everything.
她好瘦啊
She has no cellulite!
怎么可能
How can that be?
我从来没遇到过这样的
I've never seen anything like it.
从来没有
Nothing.
威尔跟我说在派对上你遇到的那个人想要你的号码
Will told me some guy you met at the party wants your number.
应该是詹森的朋友
Jason's friend, I think.
太搞笑了 我们互不来电啊
That's so funny. We both said we weren't attracted to each other.
纠结啊 他有点肥
I don't know what to do.He's kind of fat.
是吗
He is?
他有啤酒肚
He's got this big belly.
你又不会损失什么
Well, you've got nothing to lose.
我是不会 他会啊
No, but he does.
你的灯亮了 你有病人了
Your light Just came on. You got a patient.
赶紧去吧
Better get a move on.
如果你不去会发生什么
What happens if you never go out there?
他们会
Do they like...
抱歉 我是不是很无礼
Sorry. Was that inappropriate?
下次聊
Bye.
不好意思啊 我保证我预订了的
I'm sorry about this. I swear to God I made a dinner reservation.
没事啊
No, it's okay. It's fine.
跟我说说你吧 你干什么的
What about you? What do you do?
我在美国文化史图书馆工作
I work at the American Library of Cultural History.
-什么 -有点类似电视图书馆
- The what? - Exactly. It's kind of a television library.
你经常看电视吗
Do you watch a lot of TV?
不啊 我只负责放映
No, it's television history.
不过我不知道在放什么
What's on now, I have no clue.
我上次看《傻瓜镇的主妇》
I tried to watch one of those
Housewives of Idiot Town...
太难看了 我宁愿去跳楼
...but I got so depressed, I thought I was going to jump off a building.
我感同身受啊 上次和我女儿一起看
I know what you mean. I tried to watch one with my daughter...
简直不敢相信我看到的是什么
...and I could not believe what I was watching!
脑残片 整过的颧骨和胸
No brains, and the fake cheekbones and fake boobs.
你喜欢隆过的胸吗
Do you like fake boobs?
不 我喜欢天生的
No. I like real boobs.
我的没动过手术
I have real boobs.
那很好啊
That's working out for us then.
离婚多久了
How long have you been divorced?
四年了
About four years.
自愿的吗
Was it mutual?
不是
Not really. No.
能给我她的号码吗
Can I have her number?
当然
Of course.
这样多省事啊
Imagine the time that would save.
我们应该挂个牌在脖子上
We should all put a sign on our necks
写上我们的情况 一目了然
with what's wrong with us. Get it all out there.
好主意 你会写什么
Good idea. What would your sign say?
不知道 我懒的出奇 我有耳毛
I don't know. I'm a slob. I have ear hair.
你可以把耳毛脱掉的啊
There are things to get rid of that ear hair.
已经没了
Researched, taken care of.
所以你很懒 对吗
So you're a slob, huh?
不过不是脏东西囤积起来的那种
Not like a dirty hoarder slob.
那是哪种
What kind?
杂乱无章吧
A normal disorganized one.
你女儿和你住吗
Does your daughter live with you?
三四天吧
Half the time.
有时她会忍无可忍 因为她和她妈妈都很爱干净
It aggravates her sometimes. The thing is she and her mother are very, very neat.
事实上 他们最爱逛的商店是
As a matter of fact,their favorite store...
我不记得了
...I don't know, it's... it's the store
有各种空盒子和收纳箱的商店
with all the empty boxes and storage.
是不是收纳箱商店（1978在美国达拉斯开张的上市的连锁商店）
The Container Store?
对 是收纳箱商店
Yes. The Container Store.
它卖给你一堆废物装你的一堆废物 好让你买更多的垃圾
The store that sells crap you can put
your crap in so you can buy more crap.
我爱那家商店 我爱垃圾
I love that store! I love crap.
我前妻也是 她把那些废物都装进可爱华丽贵重的盒子里
So did my ex-wife, and she puts it in
lovely, flowery and expensive boxes.
它们也有男性元素在里面啊
You should know, they have things
in sort of manly designs there.
男性元素
Manly designs?
像棕皮肤的牛仔啊
Yeah, like browns,
and little cowboy designs.
牛仔啊
Little cowboys.
没有共同兴趣爱好的人
I mean, come on. It's hard
to live with somebody,
就很难相处啊 你不这样认为吗
don't you think? People's habits are...
好吧 我喜欢鳄梨沙拉
Okay, listen to this.
I like guacamole.
可是我讨厌那里面的洋葱 所以我会拿块薯片
But I don't like the onions in
guacamole, so I take a chip...
搅拌它
...and swirl it
around and separate
把洋葱拿出来
the onions from
the guacamole...
我就能吃了 她看不惯
...so I can eat guacamole. Now,
that drove her bananas.
这没什么问题啊
It sounds pretty harmless.
我也这样认为 不过她还是不爽
I thought so, but by the end of
our marriage, it made her gag.
有点小题大做喔
That's not nice.
你的手
You have...
蛮好看的
...lovely hands.
我以为按摩师的手都很大
I thought, as a masseuse,
you'd have big,
很粗糙 但是你的很好
muscular hands,
but they're very lovely.
谢谢
Thank you.
你的手也不错啊
You have nice hands, too. Actually.
谢谢
Thank you.
跟船桨差不多
Kind of like paddles.
他们是不是把声音开大了
Did they just turn
the music louder?
没有啊 你年纪大了
No, I think you just got older.
不好意思 可以把声音关小一点吗
Excuse me! Do you mind turning
down the music a little?
我老了
I'm old.
抱歉 不行
No, I'm sorry.
你对我的年纪抱歉还是调低声音
No, you're sorry I'm old or that
you won't turn the music down?
女士 我没有权利去调
I'm not allowed to
change it, ma'am.
他真是友善
He's so nice!
我和年轻人代沟太大了
I find I don't like younger people.
什么
Eh?
不好意思 选错了餐厅
I'm sorry, I picked
the wrong restaurant.
我很高兴啊 东西很好吃
I'm having a great time.
This is delicious.
我听不清你在说什么 不过
I mean. I can't hear what you're saying, but...
所以你才很开心吧
That's probably why you're
having a great time.
这是西红柿吗
What is this, tomatoes?
你开玩笑吗 这是西瓜啦
Tomatoes? It's watermelon.
旁边是油炸面包
That's croutons next to it.
你故意的吗
Doesn't that defeat the purpose?
这是脱脂酸奶 不是冰淇淋 要加点东西上去
It's nonfat yogurt, not ice cream.
You can put little stuff on it.
看起来不错
That looks good, man.
怎么了
What? What?
他们在试吃吗
People tasting?
相信你自己 直接选东西
Take a chance. Put something in your bowl.
又不是买房子
You're not buying a house.
他快乐就好啊
He's happy.
明白 把碗给我
I know. Give me this.
这么多种口味 他们都要试试
They have to test the flavors,
there's so many millions of them.
非常莓果冰糕
Very Berry Sorbet, and...
这是我女儿
This is my daughter.
天哪 她好漂亮 你太有福气了
Wowie kazowie! She's stunning! Lucky you.
谢天谢地她像她妈妈
She looks like her mother, thank God.
这是我女儿
Here's mine.
这张
Right there.
她很漂亮
She's beautiful.
你带钱了吗
You got any money?
我开玩笑呢
I'm kidding.
吓到我了
Oh, my God.
今天玩得很开心
I had such a good time.
That was really fun.
我也觉得
I thought so, too.
我还没准备好
I'm not sure.
好的
Okay.
我想说
I mean...
我的意思是或许
...I mean, maybe.
我可以理解
I understand.
就是 我也不知道
It's just... I'm not sure.
我了解 我不聋
I get it. I'm not deaf.
我确实有点聋
I'm a little deaf in...
谢谢
Thank you very much.
我喜欢摸你的手
I like your paddles.
我喜欢你的臀部
I like your ass.
天啊
My God.
谢谢
Well, thank you.
晚安
Good night.
好啊
Hi!
-好 -好
- Hi. - Hi.
怎么样
How was it?
不错
Fine.
我想说如果他马上另寻新欢 我就傻逼了
Good. I mean, if he immediately hooks up
with someone else, I'll feel like an idiot.
那就不要和他上床
So don't do it.
你们在聊什么呢
What are you talking about?
没什么
Nothing.
我不知道要不要和克里斯上床
I can't decide if I should
sleep with Chris or not.
我不想后悔莫及
I don't want to do
something I'll regret...
但是我又很喜欢他 所以很纠结啊
...but I also happen really like him,
so I don't know what to do.
你还是处女吗
And you're a virgin?
-是 -别回答
- Yeah. - Don't answer that!
你不能害怕犯错误
Ok. Here's what I say. You can't live
in fear of making a mistake.
就做就去做
If you want to do it, just do it.
-妈妈 -干吗
- Mom. - What?
别多管闲事
Stay out of it.
艾伦 是她问我的
Ellen, honey, she just asked me.
有吗
She did?
克洛伊 没有吗
Right, Chloe? No?
我的错
My bad.
我闭嘴
Quiet.
艾伦 我忘了问你
Ellen, I forgot to ask...
麦迪·普赖斯怎么了
...what happened to Maddy Price?
那天她太无礼了
Oh my god. She was so rude to me the other day!
她和赛奇·伯杰 布伦登·韦斯搞三人行
She had a threesome with
Sage Berger and Brendon Weiss...
她以为她是泰勒·莫姆森
She thinks she's Taylor Momsen.
别告诉我妈妈
Don't tell my mom!
她总是给我惊喜 你从来不会
She can tell me stuff. You never do.
等等 他们3P吗
Wait a minute. They had a threesome?
妈妈 别说了
Forget it, Mom.
现在都怎么了
What is happening?
现在他们都这样干吗
Is everybody doing it?
妈妈 住嘴
Mom, shut up!
出来吧
Come out!
你太美了
You look beautiful!
看看你们俩
Look at you two guy.
拜托
Come on!
妈妈 我才不要和你买一样的裙子
We're not buying the same dress, Mom!
我们又不会一起穿
We won't wear it at the same time.
可是你穿着不好看啊
But you look stupid.
我觉得不错
I think I look good.
太傻了
You're so lumpy!
要是我能穿我也穿了
I'd wear that if I could.
谢谢
Thank you.
你不会穿的 妈妈 你跟疯子一样
No, you wouldn't.
Mom, you look crazy.
克洛伊 我也很迷人的啊
You are not the only attractive
girl in this family, Chloe.
你为什么不能穿着像艾伦的妈妈 她多正常
Why can't you dress like Ellen's mom?
She looks normal.
你和那个严肃的男人怎么样了
So what happened with not-so-funny guy?
没下文了
It didn't work out.
-太遗憾了 -真的没事
- Oh. - No, it's fine. Really
你呢
What about you?
你有男朋友吗
Do you have a boyfriend?
我们度过了一个愉快的周末
I had a very good first
date over the weekend.
太好了 他怎么样
Oh, how nice! What's he like?
幽默风趣
Funny.
我们的话题从来没听过
And we really never stopped talking.
就像我们认识很久一样
It was like we were old friends already.
当心这会杀火花于襁褓之中
Be careful with that, 'cause
it could totally kill the chemistry.
不不不 是在好的一方面
No, no. In a good way.
我们只调调情
Really. I mean, it was just...
it was very flirtatious.
我的意思是 开始我并不喜欢他
I mean. I didn't find him
attractive at first,
他不是帅哥
You know because he's not handsome
in the typical way.
不过
But, um...
现在我觉得他有点性感了
...I don't know... now I
find him kind of... sexy.
你好
Hi.
我看错日期了吗
Did I get the day wrong?
没有啊 怎么了
No. Why?
你穿的睡衣啊
Because you're wearing pajamas?
星期天 刚吃完早午餐 这样比较舒服
It's just brunch. It's Sunday.
I like to be comfortable.
-好吧 -进来吧
- Oh, good. Okay. - Come on in.
我带的酒
I got us that.
-我去弄点含羞草 -好的
- I'll make us some mimosas. - Ok.
很好啊 谢谢
This is nice. Thank you.
你的包吗
You carry a purse?
不 是我女儿泰斯的
No, that's my daughter Tess's.
出奇的贵 不过是她十八岁生日送给她的
It was outrageously expensive, but
it was her 18th birthday, so...
天哪 百吉饼
Oh, my God! Bagels!
我大爱面包
I love bread. I really love it.
你女儿怎么样
So, what's she like? Your daughter.
她很老成 就像教科书里面讲的一样
She's very sophisticated... as
you can tell by the pocketbook.
教科书啊
"Pocketbook".
她聪明 可爱 风趣 她要搬去纽约了
She's smart, lovely and funny,
and she's moving to New York.
非常非常远
Very far away.
是很远
It is far.
她要去帕森斯大学念设计
She's going to Parsons
School of Design.
她让我很骄傲
I'm very proud of her.
肯定啊 要我也会
I bet. I would be.
不过我又不舍得让她走
But part of me thinks
that I shouldn't let her go.
她十八岁 这是个很好的机会
She's 18 and this is
a great opportunity for...
如果在纽约有什么事情发生的话
...but if something
happens to her...
我不会原谅自己的
...while she's in New York,
I will never forgive myself.
我理解你的心情
Come on. But I know what you mean.
上大学这事
This whole going away to college thing.
我们就让他们离开 我们还不知道他们的情况
We just send them off? And not
know where they are all the time?
而且我还不知道
Aside from the fact that I don't know
我女儿走了我的生活会变怎样
what my life will be like when she's gone.
艾伦都不想让我们送她
And Ellen doesn't want her dad and me
她只想我们送她到
to take her there. She wants us to take her...
机场 但是不能和她一起去
...to the airport here,
but don't fly with her.
让她自己去还不如杀了我
That would kill me...
just put her on the plane?
心碎就是就来形容这种心情的吧
Heartbreaking. That's the word for.
我们得培养点兴趣爱好
We're going to have to develop hobbies. I think.
我想是吧
Yeah, I guess so.
我已经织毛衣这个兴趣了
Because I have already have one,
'cause I knit.
所以我的计划就是织毛衣度过我余生
So I'll just spend the rest of my
life knitting. That's my plan.
说起来奇怪 因为我也会织
That's funny because...actually, I weave.
织篮筐吗
Like baskets?
-对啊 我在车库里织 -真的吗
- Yeah, I do it in the garage. - Really!
肯定不是啊
No.
为什么会认为我会织东西啊
Why would you think I'd weave?
我以为你 我没有别的意思
I thought you were...
I didn't want to insult you.
-你不会真是太好了 -我也是
- I'm kind of glad you don't weave. I have to say.
- Me, too.
我一直在想没有她在的日子会是怎样的
You know, I've been picturing what it's going
to be like for her not to be here.
虽然她只呆三四天 也是个巨大的改变啊
Even though she's only here half
the time, it'll be very different.
我看到你丁丁了
Look. I can see your penis.
什么 我的天
What? My God!
你的睡衣太透了
Your pajama thing is a little bit open.
擦 不好意思
Shit! I'm very sorry.
你觉得怎么样
What did you think?
我觉得你很健康
I think you are very healthy.
谢谢
Thank you.
换条裤子行吗
Go change your pants. Ok?
马上就好
Be right back.
你们怎么了 大概说一下就好 不要细节
What happened to you guys? Not
the details, obviously, just general...
我们非常不一样
We were... very different.
我们没有嘿咻过 不是我不想要
We never had sex. Not my choice.
而是她没有性趣
She just had no interest in it.
我敢肯定她外面有人了
And I'm pretty sure she had an affair.
太不爽了
Which was awful,
因为这说明她喜欢嘿咻的
because it meant
that she did like sex,
只是不喜欢和我做爱
she just didn't like it with me.
你是对的
You. Right.
她认为我的工作太愚蠢了
She thought my job was stupid.
我们互相指责对方不会养小孩
She thought I parented badly.
I thought she parented badly.
你为什么在搞破坏
Why are you wrecking my backyard?
太多杂草了
You have a lot of weeds.
这很好啊
I thought this was all good.
不
No.
我们也没有嘿咻过 也不是他的问题
We never had sex, either. Not his choice.
我们是不同世界的人
We were pretty out of
sync in that department.
跟艾伦在一起的时候我们也没有相同的频率
We were pretty out of sync
with Ellen, too. Oh, my God...
关于如何养育小孩争的你死我活
...fought all the time
about how to parent.
你拔的不是杂草
That's good grass you're pulling up.
我放回去
I'll put it back.
老天
Jesus.
你脚上
Got yourself a...
起泡了吗
...blister thing going on?
是的
Yeah.
你觉得恶心吗
Are you grossed out?
没有
No.
你有 你害怕看我的脚吗
You are. Are you
freaked out by my feet?
有一点
I have a little problem with feet.
那你有看过你自己的脚吗
Have you looked at your own feet?
自己的无所谓
I'm used to my feet.
好吧
Okay, well...
为什么
What's the deal?
跟我妈有点关系
It has to do with my mother.
她脚臭吗
She had feet?
她有双令人过目不忘的脚
She had spectacular feet.
洗耳恭听啊
Here we go.
青一块紫一块的
They were red and
yellow and green
还有肿大
and purple and
swollen with veins.
我懂了
I get it.
你不用穿上鞋啊
Don't do that.
我必须穿啊 我从来没有修过指甲
I have to. I've never had a pedicure.
除非有毛病我从来不管它
I never saw the point until this actual moment.
你要创可贴吗
Would you like a Band-Aid?
那太好了
Please! That would be great.
再来个袋子包住我的脚吧
And maybe a bag for my foot.
别傻了
Stop it.
拿两个好替换啊
Two bags. Two bags for the old bag.
我就知道不该告诉你的
I knew I shouldn't have told you.
他们裸着的 对吧
They're naked, right?
是的
Yeah.
你有被他们吸引吗
Are you ever attracted to them?
不会
No. I never.
他们肯定对你有兴趣
I'm sure they're attracted to you.
这我就不清楚了 他们是来做按摩的
Well I don't know. They're getting massaged.
他们有挑逗你吗
Do they ever hit on you?
有时候会
Sometimes, yeah.
如果你需要的话改天给你按摩下
I can give you a massage
some time, if you want.
我很有兴趣
I think I might like that.
不过我觉得会挑逗你的
But I would definitely hit on you.
没问题啊
That might be okay.
真的吗
Really?
可以亲你吗
Want a kiss?
可以
Yeah.
你没有睁开你眼镜 对吧
You didn't actually open your
eyes at any point, did you?
不需担心
No. No worries.
我没睁开眼
I kept my eyes closed.
我想着
I figured...
你看不到我 我也看不到你
...if I couldn't see you,
you couldn't see me.
我偷看了你
Oh, I saw you.
天哪
Oh, God.
我讨厌幽默的自己
I'm tired of being funny.
我也是
Me, too.
可是你又不幽默
But you're not funny.
我为你感到高兴 他听起来很不错
I'm so excited for you.
He sounds really great.
他是不错 他还做了早午餐
He is great. It was so cute...
he made a whole bruncheon.
-好贴心啊 -对啊
- Sweet. - Yeah, it was sweet.
好了
Okay, good.
嘿咻的感觉太棒了
We had such good sex.
难以想象
How fun. I can't even imagine.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
我喜欢以前摆放的样子 不要放弃治疗
I liked how it was before. You're going
to give yourself a hernia. You know.
好了 不用你们帮忙了 谢谢你们
Okay, you guys are done.
Thanks for your help.
拿上你们的画去厨房
Take your drawing
in the kitchen.
可以看电视 不过不能看克里夫兰秀
You can watch TV,
but no Cleveland Show.
妈妈 求你了
Please, Mom?
好吧
Okay.
天啊 你应该坚定立场的
Jeez. Way to put your foot down.
当父母太累了
I'm too tired to be a good parent.
也许是因为你总是爱摆弄家具
Maybe because you're always
moving furniture around.
-凯茜你好 -好啊
- Hi, Cathy! - Hola.
你绝对不知道 威尔不肯炒了她
You have no idea. Will
refused to fire her...
我也不管了 希望她能更好点 但是她变本加厉
...so I let it go, hoping she'd
get better. But she got worse.
她想做些蠢事 让我们炒了她
It was like she wanted to be fired.
She did such dumb stuff.
好有趣 不是吗
That is so interesting, isn't it?
所以我解雇了她 她开始哭 我也哭
So I fired her. And she started crying.
Then I started crying.
然后我们用拥抱着 我又把她请回来了
Then we were hugging and...
I hired her back.
这就是你的作风 因为你是个老好人
Of course you did. See, cause you're nice.
会吗 他们都认为我富有同情心
Right? Some people would see
me as being compassionate
或者心太软什么的
or soft-hearted or whatever.
威尔觉得我还是个孩子
Will thinks I'm a baby.
他想我炒了她当成学习
He wants me to fire her again
as a learning experience!
我的天哪
Jesus Christ!
我们的关系就这样
That's our relationship.
-拜托 你们又不是一直这样 -管它呢
- Come on, this is not your whole
relationship. - Whatever.
他就是个没人爱的孩子 永不满足
He's a middle child who never got
enough fried chicken at dinner table
还希望事事公平
and needs everything to be fair.
莎拉女士 这个应该放哪 在厕所发现的
Miss Sarah? Where should I put this?
It was in the bathroom.
放外面的兵乓球桌上
Outside, with the
ping pong table.
好的
Okay. No problem.
天啊
Jesus.
哇
Wow.
我还没见过智齿呢
I've never actually seen wisdom teeth.
你有牙体缺失啊
You do have a lot of fillings.
你觉得严重吗
Do you think they are the mercury kind, though?
一般
The normal kind.
还有几个齿冠
And a couple of crowns.
好吧 该你了
Yeah. Okay, your turn.
我 还是算了吧
Well, I'd rather you didn't.
我就要
Well, I'd rather I did.
我先拿下眼睛
Excuse me, I'm going to get my glasses.
-张嘴 -不要 -张嘴啊 -不要
- Come on. - No. - Open your mouth! - No.
-张嘴 -你想办法啊
- Open your mouth. - Make me.
想办法啊
Make me.
-张嘴 -好
- Open your mouth. - Okay.
天哪 你少了一颗牙齿
Oh, my God! You're missing a tooth?
-真的 -对啊
- You are! - Yes, I am.
让我看看
Let me see.
没多大问题
You can't tell... it's way back there.
It doesn't matter.
需要做个可怕的植骨手术
I need some kind of hideous bone graft.
费用太高了 没做
It costs a lot of money and I'm putting it off.
我奶奶迪迪做过
My grandma Dee Dee had that.
你奶奶迪迪 谢谢
Your grandma Dee Dee.
Thank you for that. Thanks.
抱歉
Oh, I'm so sorry!
没关系 她是艾伦的闺蜜克洛伊 这是我朋友艾伯特
It's okay. This is Ellen's best friend,
Chloe. This is my friend, Albert.
你好
Hi.
艾伦没有回我短信 我以为她还在睡觉呢
Ellen didn't answer my texts.
So I thought maybe she was sleeping.
她在她爸爸那 有什么事吗
She's at her dad's, honey.
Is everything okay?
我们约好出去吃早饭的
I thought we were go out
getting breakfast.
你饿了没
You hungry?
我想想 一九七五年的第四频道有什么节目
Let's see. From 1975, Channel 4.
什么时间
Well, what time?
别闹了
Oh, come on.
星期六早上
Saturday morning.
《啄木鸟伍迪》 《粉红豹》 《麦克达夫》 《会说话的狗》
Woody Woodpecker, Pink Panther,
McDuff, the Talking Dog...
虽然我不喜欢 不过还是看了
...which I didn't
like but watched anyway,
《怪物小分队》 《失落的大陆》 然后是
Monster Squad,
Land of the Lost, then...
《大小约翰》很像电影《巨大》 不过更怪异些
...Big John, Little John, which was
like the movie Big, but much weirder.
太不可思议了
Ok, That's incredible.
我以为我看的电视够多了
I thought I watched a lot of TV!
我以前会看电视节目表
I looked forward to that lineup.
什么 你是没人照看的小孩吗
What, were you neglected as a kid?
我就像放养的小牛一样
I was kind of raised like a veal.
关进黑屋
I was put in a dark room...
有吃的 叫我别乱走
...fed and told not to move.
神清气爽啊
Very relaxing.
她说 我想要其他的尺码
...and she's like, "I
might want to get another size",
那是扯淡啊 明明就是正确的尺码
but that's bullshit, it is the right size.
她身材娇小 可是上围很大 所以给了她中码
She's petite, but very heavy
on top, so I got a medium!
后来又悲剧了 我在诺德斯特龙折扣店买的
But here's the thing,
I got it at Nordstrom Rack,
却放进了尼曼的盒子里
but I put it in a Neiman Marcus box...
很好
Oh, yeah, that's good.
最好别开门
Don't open the door.
就假装你不知道我来了
Just pretend you don't know I'm here...
虽然你听到了我关车门的声音
...even though you heard me lock my car.
哇
Wow!
太棒了
Amazing.
你们拿着干吗的
So what do you do with all this?
-你真的想听吗 -对啊 怎么了
- Do you really want to hear this?
- Yeah. I do. What?
我确保它们转化成电子版
I make sure things are
transferred to digital properly.
确保它们正常播放 我还写它们的简介
I make sure they're logged in properly.
I write blurbs...
当有五十岁以下的人想过来
...so if anyone under 50 wants to
put down their phone and come in...
找原版的话 他们就可以找到他们想要的东西
...and watch something original and brilliant,
they can find it what they are looking for.
比如说
Like what, for instance?
《席德·西泽秀》《杰克·本尼秀》
The Sid Caesar show.
The Jack Benny show.
《狄恩·马汀秀》
The Dean Martin show.
-好棒啊 -对啊
- So cool. - Yeah, it is.
我乐在其中
I kind of love it.
无聊的时候
On slow days...
我就会坐在办公室 看几集《发生什么了》
...I can sit downstairs on my office and
watching couple episodes of What's Happening!!
你在开玩笑
No, you don't.
如果
Well, if things...
这是我办公室
This is my office.
那是鲍勃
That's Bob. Hey.
-你看过《海豚的故事》（1996年上映美国家庭冒险片）吗 -当然
- What about Flipper? Did you ever
see Flipper? - Of course I did.
当时好想要一只海豚当做宠物啊
Oh, God. It made me want a
dolphin as a pet so bad.
真的吗 那要费很多功夫啊
Really? That's a lot of work.
那是什么声音
What is that noise?
有人在看伤感的电影 不足为奇
Somebody watching something.
It happens occasionally.
这是《的士速递》 这里阿历克斯的狗狗死了
It's Taxi. The episode
where Alex's dog dies.
狗狗是他的兄弟
Buddy or Buster or something.
-饿了吗 -饿死了
- You hungry? - Yeah I'm starving.
吃中饭去吧
Let's get lunch.
她来了 真准时
There she is! Right on time.
-好啊 -好啊 爸爸
- Hi, honey. - Hi, Dad.
这是伊娃
So, Eva...
这是泰斯
Tess. Tess, Eva.
很高兴见到你
Hi. Nice to meet you.
我也是
So nice to meet you, too.
真的在这家吃吗
Seriously?
它们家的辣椒很棒啊
They have great chili!
我喜欢辣椒
I love Chili.
你们有去过丽丽那吃过吗
Have you ever been to Lilly's?
没
No.
妙不可言啊 就在这附近
It's so good.
It's right around the corner.
那就去那吧
Lilly's it is.
我学的是时装设计
I'll be studying fashion design.
你的品位不错
You obviously have good taste.
谢谢
Thank you.
伊娃的女儿也是在秋天去上大学
Eva has a daughter your age going
to college in the fall also.
她去莎拉劳伦斯学院
She's going to Sarah Lawrence.
她对英文和历史很感兴趣 特别是历史
She's interested in English and history.
She loves history!
她想成为一名作家
I think she wants to be a writer.
但是莎拉劳伦斯和以前大不相同了
But Sarah Lawrence is
not what it used to be.
我的意思是还是挺不错的
I mean, I'm sure it's still good.
只是最近几年在走下坡路 我的一些
It's just gone downhill a lot in the
last few years. Some of my, um...
不怎么聪明的朋友都被录取了 我简直不敢相信
...let's just say not-so-smart
friends just got in. I was shocked.
-我相信还是会有才华的人的 -对啊
-Well. I'm sure a lot of smart people
still go there. - Oh, yeah.
我只是说说而已
I know. I'm just saying.
我还是愿意你上这边的大学
I think you should stay
home and go to school here.
至少你说的是真心话
At least you're honest about it.
妈妈就假装很兴奋可以享受一人生活了 我才不信
Mom acts like she's excited to be on
her own again, but I don't buy it.
对你妈好点 她很不错的
Why don't we take it a little easy on Mom.
Ok? She's all right.
也许你有小孩就懂了
And maybe you should judge till you
have kids of your own.
可惜的是我不想要孩子
Except I'm not having any.
何出此言
And why do you say that?
我是事业型的
I want a career.
也不喜欢孩子
Anyway, I hate kids.
真的假的
Really?
跟我想法一样
Right now we have that in common.
科里
Corey?
她在说胡话呢
Listen, she doesn't know
what she's talking about.
她还太小了 成熟了就明白了
She's too young to know what she wants.
We don't have to worry.
爸 我去喝咖啡了
Dad, I'm going to go
get a coffee, okay?
拜拜 谢谢你的午饭
Bye. Thank you for lunch.
-见到你真好 -我也是
- So nice to met you. - You, too.
很好
Yeah. Great.
-拜拜 -下次见
- Bye! - Bye.
小心点
Be careful!
她朋友好多啊
She has a lot of friends.
你觉得她会3P吗
You think she has threesomes?
什么 为什么这么说
What? Why would you say that?
他们年轻人都爱这个啊
I know, but apparently, it's
what they're doing these days.
我听说的
That's what I heard.
天哪
Oh, my God.
很震惊 对吧
Right?
恐怕那扇窗户关上了
I'm afraid that window's closed.
有窗户吗
There was a window?
他女儿怎么样
How was the daughter?
说实话 感觉不好 好假啊
Kind of awful, actually. A real snob.
太糟糕了吧
That's too bad.
我在想你室友会是怎么样的
I wonder what your roommate will be like?
我也是
Me, too.
你想我和他们父母先联系吗
You want me to call her parents?
不要
No, I don't.
你饿了吗
You hungry, honey?
还没
Not really.
你昨天吃的什么
What did you eat yesterday?
不知道
I don't know.
我想知道你昨天吃了什么
Well, think. Tell me.
I want to know what you ate.
麦片
Cereal...
一根香蕉
...a banana...
-你在哪吃的香蕉 -妈妈 别乱想
- Where'd you get the banana?
- Mom, you're crazy!
什么
What?
那中午吃的什么
What'd you have for lunch though?
好了 我要走了
Okay, bye.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
我的意思是 他中年了又很肥 不过我不介意
I mean, he's kind of flabby and
middle-aged, but I don't care.
我也和他一样
I'm flabby and middle-aged.
搞笑的是我的中年
It's funny, because our
middle-agedness is...
对我来说是件很舒适愉快的一件事
...comforting, and sexy to me.
是不是很悲催 不过同时也很好
Isn't that so incredibly sad?
But sort of good too.
对啊 我前夫就是
Yeah. I think that my ex, all he
wanted was for me to accept...
大肚子 还有一堆怪癖
...his belly and all of his quirks.
后来是完全没性趣
In the end, I was completely
repulsed by him sexually.
性生活太不和谐了
Kind of terrible in bed
and just very clumsy.
不会吧
Oh, god no.
等等
Just a sec.
这是我最后一本书 不过我想给你
Here. It's my last copy, but I
really want you to have it.
真的吗
Wow! Are you sure?
-真的啊 -哇
- Absolutely. - Oh, wow.
有点不安啊 我不太懂诗歌啊
I'm a little intimidated. I'm
not really good with poetry.
让它灌溉你就好 不用理解
Just let it wash over you.
Don't try to understand it.
相信我 我不会的 非常感谢
I won't, believe me.
God, thank you so much!
-我们相处的很融洽啊 -是啊
- I've loved our time together.
- I know.
你觉得我们以朋友的身份出去玩会不会很奇特
Do you think it would be weird
if we hung out as friends?
不会啊 很好啊
I would love that! I would!
尝尝这沙拉吧 这西红柿太棒了
I want you to try this salsa,
'cause these tomatoes are amazing.
注意里面有很多洋葱
But careful! There's a ton of onions.
我离婚之后的一大好处
One of the many upsides to my divorce.
-什么意思 -我前夫讨厌洋葱 他会拿块薯片
- What do you mean? - My ex hated
onions, so he would take a chip...
放到沙拉里
...and he would put it in the
salsa and tap, tap, tap...
鼓捣鼓捣
...swirl, tap, tap, tap,
swirl, and so on,
直到洋葱
until all the onions
were pushed...
都在一边
...up against the side!
简直不能忍受
It kind of made me sick.
妈妈
Mom?
那是我女儿 她不太舒服 等等
That's my daughter... she's not
feeling well. Be right back.
-宝贝 -好啊
- Hi, honey. - Hi.
我不舒服
I don't feel good.
-就在这 -我看看
- I feel... Right here. - Let me see.
有点肿大
They're swollen.
见见我朋友 就一会
Listen, will you come meet my friend?
Just for a second, please?
伊娃
Eva?
你在哪
太奇怪了 刚刚还在这的 伊娃
That's so weird, she was just here. Eva?
我睡觉去了
I'm going back to bed.
-爱你 -我也爱你 你口臭啊
- I love you. - I love you, too.
You have bad breath.
我生病啊
I'm sick!
天哪
God!
你在这啊
Hi.
这课树好大啊
This planting I'm
admiring, it's so huge!
谢谢
Thank you.
我想让你见见我女儿泰斯的 不过
I wanted you to meet my
daughter Tess, but...
我有其他事情要做
I have to go.
哦
Okay!
好的
Yeah. Okay.
很好
Great!
好的
All right.
下周电话联系 好吗
So I'll call you next week and
we'll do something. Ok?
很好 谢谢
Wonderful. Thank you so much!
太好了
It was so nice!
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
玩的愉快
Have a great day.
很愉快
Great, great, great!
拜拜
Bye-bye.
-还好吗 -没事
- You okay? - I got it!
你相信吗 我可没有吓你
Do you believe that?
I am not shitting you!
太巧合了吧 当时怎么想的
That is an unbelievable coincidence.
What you gonna do?
大脑一片空白
I don't know!
该死 你又有病人了 待会再聊吧
Oh, shit! Your light went on.
Can you call me back, please?
妈妈
Hi, Mom!
你脱鞋了吗
Hi! Did you take your shoes off?
没有 什么时候需要脱鞋了啊
No. Since when do I have to?
现在 这样更干净 还有袜子也脱了
We're doing that now. It's cleaner.
And your socks, too.
你们绝不会相信的
You are not going to believe this.
我按摩的那女的居然是艾伯特的前妻
It turns out that the woman I've
been massaging is Albert's ex-wife.
-狗血啊 -非常狗血
- Weird! - So weird.
我听她说着
I have been listening to her say the
worst things about the one guy...
我刚有好感的人的坏话
...I started to really, really like.
我还在想着她前夫一副
And I pictured the ex she was
talking about as this fat...
肥头大耳的样子
...irritating slob...
没想到居然是艾伯特
...and it turns
out it's Albert!
肥猪艾伯特
Fat Albert!
什么 谁啊
What? Who?
我说动画片呢
It's a cartoon. A cartoon!
但是他不想是这样啊
But he's so not like that.
你怎么知道
How do you know?
那天我们一起吃的早饭 他很幽默风趣啊
We had breakfast the other day.
He's sweet, funny.
你也喜欢他 对吧
Yeah, you liked him, right? Did you like him?
-绝对啊 -等等 什么
- Totally. - Wait, what?
那天你不在 我们一起吃的早饭
You weren't here, honey.
We all had breakfast. That's all.
我还没过他呢
I haven't even met him.
有机会的啦
Well, you will.
-她说他什么坏话了 -天哪
- What did she say about him?
- Oh, my God!
简直贬到一无是处啊 很恶心啊
It's like this parade of horribles!
He's disgusting.
床上技术很烂
That he's like this clown in bed.
妈妈 别说这么露骨
Mom! Oh, my God!
不好意思
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
我约过几次会 不过机会不多
I date sometimes. It's just
so hard to meet people.
而且很难喜欢上别人
And I'm not attracted to anybody.
-真的吗 -真的
- Really? - Really.
你也没有喜欢过你前夫吗
And you weren't attracted
to your ex-husband?
这太糟糕了吧
That must have been difficult.
我试着去接受过的
Well, I tried
really hard. I did.
他骗我说他都在吃素食
But he would go on so many diets,
and then he would cheat...
实际上没有 对于变胖这个事实
...and then he would act
shocked when he got fatter.
他也是无所谓
...the behavior
around the weight.
打扰下
Excuse me.
你是玛丽安妮·霍普吗
Are you Marianne Hope?
对
Yes.
-我的天哪 -跟你说了是她吧
- Oh, my God! - I told you.
我们刚还说到你呢 你是我们的偶像
We were just talking about you.
You are like our biggest idol.
你的书对我们的生活太重要了
This means so much to us.
我妈妈去世的时候她给了我一本《美丽果实》
She gave me a copy of Beautiful
Fruit when my mom died.
它让我挺过来了
It saved me.
太好了 很遗憾听到你妈妈去世的消息
How wonderful. I'm so sorry.
谢谢
Oh, thank you.
非常感谢 祝你好运
Well, thanks very much. Blessings.
好运
Blessings.
祝你们好运
Take care. Blessings!
你是活菩萨啊
It's so cool that you saved her.
不过他没有肥胖症 对吗
But, he never got obese, right?
那要看你的理解啦
Well, it depends on your
definition of the word obese.
刚开始 你是有
But initially, um... you were...
你或多或少有喜欢他的吧
...I don't know, you
liked him, more or less?
很少
Unfortunately... less.
很多事情我都看不惯
There were just so many things
that really got on my nerves.
比如说
Like what, though?
抱歉 我又消极了
Sorry I'm being so negative.
I really am.
没事啊
But it's okay. It is.
我没有朋友
It's just that I don't really have anybody
可以让我抱怨这些事
I can bitch to about things like this.
你可以向我吐苦水啊
You can completely bitch to me. Really.
-谢谢 -没关系啊
- Thank you. - Oh, sure.
我很信任你
I trust you.
天哪
Oh, god.
真的
I do.
你什么毛病啊 她可以另找一个按摩师啊
What's wrong with you?
She can find another masseuse.
我是她朋友 她没有好朋友
I'm her friend. She doesn't
have any close friends.
我喜欢和她在一起的感觉
I'm like it.
我深陷其中不能自拔 -她就像人生导师一样
I feel so pulled in.
She's like a human Trip Advisor.
艾伯特又不是旅馆 你看看别人的评价就做出选择
Albert is not a hotel.
可是有机会了解下也不是坏事啊
But if you could avoid staying
in a bad one, wouldn't you?
天哪
Oh, my God.
她说了他很多坏习惯
She has said so many
bad things about him.
她也并非善类
She's not perfect.
她知道她在说什么 她不傻
But she knows what she's talking about.
She's smart.
你也是啊
So are you.
也许她是对的
Maybe she's ultimately right.
那彼得呢 就因为你不爱他了 他就一无是处了吗
Are you right about Peter? Couse you just didn't
want him... does that make him unlovable?
还是有人会喜欢他的
By anyone normal.
我家具摆放的怎么样
You haven't said anything about
my furniture arrangement.
我都忘了原来怎么样
I don't remember how it was before.
你觉得怎么样
Hey! What do you think?
亲爱的 你有强迫症啊
Oh, honey. Why do you keep doing this?
她在排遣空虚呢
She's filling a hole.
放着我来
I'll fill your hole.
别乱想
Different hole.
机不可失失不再来 好好玩吧
You're missing out. Fun time!
你好
Hi!
谁的车啊
Whose car is this?
泰斯的车拿去修了 这是租的
Tess is getting hers fixed.
This is a rental.
不好意思
Sorry.
那怎么在你这
Why do you have it?
我让她开我的 她更喜欢我的车
I'm letting her drive mine.
She likes it better.
肯定啊
Yeah, I bet she does.
-可以吗 -没问题
- You okay? - Yeah.
那是什么
What was that?
车子在卖萌呢
The gear skrinkle.
卖萌啊 （skrinkle查不到 因为汽车有发出声音 所以这样翻译）
"Skrinkle?"
干吗要晃它
Why are you shaking that?
把黄油弄均匀
It spreads the butter around.
你要了很多黄油吗
You put more butter on that?
没有啊 就一般的量啊
No, I put regular butter. I asked
for butter. I didn't put more butter.
哦 我以为原来就有的呢
Oh, I thought it came with butter.
这个演员 我在餐厅见过他
This actor, this guy, I saw him in a restaurant.
三尺半的身高
He was about three and a half feet tall.
轻点声 好吗
You need to whisper, okay?
她穿的什么啊 好像她姨妈
What is she wearing?
It looks like her aunt
在编什么搭在盆栽上
crocheted something
to put over like a plant or something.
嘘
Shh!
小点声
You got to whisper.
我是轻声说的啊
I am whispering.
- 我是轻声说的啊 - 你没有
- I'm whispering. - No.
我问你些事情
I want to ask you something.
我要你实话实说
And I really want the truth.
问吧
Okay.
我压着你还能呼吸吗
Can you breathe when I'm on top of you?
可以啊
Yeah!
是时候开始减肥了
I'm planning on losing some weight.
By the way. I know I need to.
-你前妻也抱怨过这个问题吗 -天啊
- Was it an issue with your ex-wife?
- Oh, my God!
有时候我吃的东西也会让她不解
Sometimes I ate just to drive her nuts.
你感冒了吗
You have a cold?
不 没有
No. No, I...
我鼻子受过几次伤
I broke my nose a couple times.
医生说我鼻子已经没有实际用处了
My doctor says at this point,
my nose is purely ornamental.
想要做手术吗
Will you get it fixed?
要啊 先把牙齿弄好再说
Yeah, after the missing tooth.
我觉得很泰斯喜欢你
You know, I think Tess really liked you.
能感觉出来
I could tell.
她很好
She seems so neat.
她很不错的
She really is a great girl.
只是有时候很讨人嫌 不过
I know she can be obnoxious
sometimes, but...
她的出发点是好的 她还小 她长大后会明白的
...she's young. She's really got
a good heart. She's gonna figure it out.
我被你迷住了
I kind of adore you already.
你和克里斯怎么样啦
So what about you and Chris?
What's going on there?
说啊
What? What?
我们嘿咻了
We did it.
真的吗
Really?
感觉怎么样
How was it?
很好啊 其实
Nice. I think.
是很棒
No, it was good.
恭喜啊 我很高兴
Congratulations. I'm happy it was nice.
就算我们分开了 我也不会后悔
Even if we don't stay together,
I'm glad I got it over with.
感谢你的建议
I'm glad I took your advice.
你回来啦
Hey! Hi, honey.
你什么时候到的
When did you get here?
刚到 在等你呢
A couple of minutes ago.
Just waiting for you.
呃
Look.
我早就想帮你涂指甲油了
I've wanted to paint your
nails for like ten years.
我以为你只是怕痒呢
I thought you were too ticklish.
我是啊
I know!
她恋爱了
She's in love.
爱情的力量的无穷的啊
So I guess that makes you not
ticklish anymore.
你刚才没在 来聊聊吧
You weren't here. Come be with us.
其实我有一些
Actually, I have some...
别走啊 艾伦
Come on, Ellen. Come back.
疯狂的一天
Crazy day.
今早接到琼尼·米切尔的电话
I had a wonderful call from
Joni Mitchell this morning.
她去看了我的展览并给了好评
She read the galleys to my new collection
and loved them, so that was...
你是琼尼·米切尔的朋友吗
You're friends with Joni Mitchell?
对啊 认识她有一阵子了 要喝水吗
Yeah, we have been for a while.
Do you want some water?
不用 谢谢
No, thank you.
我遇见一个非常不错的男人
And I met a guy! A really nice guy.
他非常懂得照顾自己 他是素食主义者
He takes really good care
of himself. He's vegan...
他有看过我的书
...and he actually read
my work before he met me.
我的天哪 会读诗歌的素食者
A poetry-reading vegan. Oh, my God!
希望能有个好结果
I hope it goes well.
我的希望又重燃了
I tend to get my hopes up a little early.
不要再让我失望就好
I just don't want to be disappointed again.
this bait and switch going on、
艾伯特让我失望透了
With Albert, there was always
第一次约会的时候 我还想
When we first started dating, I thought,
他是土豪啊 还有钱买房子
"Oh, he's mature. He can buy a house."
- 这栋房子吗 - 是的
- This house? - Yes!
看看他现在的家 还有他用
But you should see where he lives now.
And he made...
茄子和玛苏里拉奶酪做的意大利面
...this dish of spaghetti
with eggplant and mozzarella.
听起来很好吃的样子
Sounds kind of delicious.
不过他只会做那一道
But it turned out that
was all he could cook.
他没有朋友 我也没有 不过
And he has no friends.
I mean, neither do I, but...
我和琼尼是你的朋友啊
Well, me and Joni.
那倒是
Yeah. That's true! That's true, that's true.
你好
Hi.
-饿了吗 -是啊
- Hungry? - Yes.
尝尝这意大利面
Get ready for some
eggplant with mozzarella!
-你没事吧 -没事啊
- You okay? - Yeah.
还蛮好吃的啊
Wow! This is actually delicious!
干吗这么惊讶
Why do you sound surprised?
很不错啊
It's great.
今天工作怎么样
How was work today?
很好
It was good.
有两位客人
I had two massages.
一言不发还是
Barnacles?
说个没完 还是勃起男
Non-stop talking? Boners?
有一位来自圣莫尼卡的女士
There was this nice woman in Santa Monica.
她说了很多关于她前夫的事
She talked a lot about her ex-husband.
不会是我前妻吧
I just hope it wasn't my ex-wife.
我
I
我给你准备了个小礼物
I got you a little present.
是吗
You did?
小礼物
Now, it's just a little present.
天哪
Oh, my God!
我一看到她就想到了你
I saw it and thought of you.
这条美丽的
This beautiful, wonderful...
我帮你带上吧
I can't do it, but let me help you.
天哪
Oh, my God.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
我戴着
Look.
好看吗
Do you like it on me?
很好看啊
It's nice.
现在送你这个是不是太早了
Maybe I shouldn't have? Is it too soon?
不会啊 我很喜欢
No. It's just so nice.
谢谢
Thank you.
啊
Oh!
-怎么了 -没事
- What? - Nothing.
-还好吧 -抱歉 不知道那是什么
- You all right? - Yeah. I don't
know what that was. Sorry.
-我来吧 -确定没事吗
- Let me get here. - You okay?
-不要 -又怎么了 -你的胡子太刺人了
- Stop! Stop! -What?
- Your beard is so tickly.
不好意思
Sorry.
没事
That's okay.
那继续吧
Okay, here I come again.
我的头发
Oh, my hair! My hair, my hair!
不知道怎么了 要不下次吧
I don't know what I'm doing, but this
isn't going very well, so let's just stop.
怎么了
What?
穿上我的睡袍很好看
You look cute in my robe.
-没事吧 -你的漱口水也泰国了吧
- Is everything okay? - You have
like four hundred mouthwashes.
我需要就买了
Yeah, I need to use them and...
不过我忘记我买过了 就又买了更多
...then I buy them and then I forget
about them and then I buy more of them.
牙刷也很多
And you have like 80 million toothbrushes.
有吗
I do?
我只用一只
I only use one of them.
那为什么不扔了其他的
So why don't you throw the other ones out?
不知道 因为有感情了
I don't know. Because... they're my friends?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
要不要再试一次
You want to take another shot at it?
我有点累了
I'm just... I'm kind of tired.
-下次好吗 -可以啊
- Is that okay? - Totally.
你好美啊
You looked so pretty.
说真的 我非常骄傲
Seriously, kiddo, I'm proud of you.
谢谢 爸爸
Thank you, Dad.
我们都非常骄傲
We are so proud.
这是庆祝你毕业的奖金
We have some graduation money for you.
谢谢你们
Thank you, Fran, Dad.
全是五块的哦
It's in fives.
谢谢你们邀请我
Thank you for including me.
你真和你吗吵架了啊
You really have a fight with your mom?
-大吵了一架 -你爸呢
- Huge. - Where's your dad?
他在圣地亚哥 不过好像他在阿拉斯加一样
He lives in San Diego, but
you'd think he was in Alaska.
他从不来看我
He never visits.
不过我无所谓了
But I don't care.
他和一个好像哑巴的女人结婚了
He remarried this really weird
woman, and she never talks.
好好听听人家的经历
Hear, hear for second marriages!
不过有一点倒是真的
It's kind Of true, though.
年长的和更加睿智的会愈加适合
It's good when everyone is older and wiser.
更加稳定
Steady.
也许二次婚姻顺利的关键在于你不怎么计较了
Maybe second marriages work because
people have figured out how to compromise.
或者懂得怎么样才是得体的
Or behave. Perhaps.
-谢谢 -没人说你
- Thank you very much.
- Nobody's talking about you.
别对号入座 我说的是一般情况
Don't take it personally.
I'm talking generally.
如果我要再婚的话 绝对不自找麻烦
If I got married again, I'd be on the
lookout for the inevitable problems.
多么奇怪的谈话啊
Odd conversation. Pretty weird.
不好意思 我想你没有机会的
Sorry, but maybe don't get
married a second time.
我只是说说而已 何况鬼知道呢
I'm not saying I will. I'm just saying.
她只是随口说说
She's just saying.
弗兰 你前夫怎么样
Fran, what was your ex-husband,
you first husband like?
他其实是个很好的男人 只是不适合我
Oh, he was actually a lovely, lovely man.
But not for me.
很理性啊
Very grownup!
他两年前去世了
He passed away. Two years ago.
不好意思
Oh, I'm sorry.
可以帮我们再拿一些面包过来吗
Sorry. Could we get some more bread, please?
-不要面包啦 -为什么
- Please, no more bread. - Why not?
-我吃饱了 -那就别吃啊
- I don't want to eat it. - Then don't eat it.
再拿些面包
More bread, please.
你还要吃吗
Are you even gonna eat it?
不知道 不过其他人可能想吃啊
I don't know, but somebody else might want some.
-我想吃 -我也是
- I probably will. - Me, too.
有两位想吃面包的啊
Bread eater, bread eater.
所以 弗兰 你喜欢吃面包啊
I'm sorry. So, Fran, you eat bread, I see.
对啊
It's true!
所以说你们家一直都用饼干咯
So that means you get to keep cookies
in  the house all the time.
可以啊
I can.
你们在说什么啊
What are you guys talking about?
没什么 不过我自控力不好
It's not a big deal, but I have a little
trouble controlling myself...
每次彼得带回家的巧克力啊
...so when Peter would
bring home things like...
面包啊 或者其他好吃的
...chocolate or good
bread, yummy stuff,
我都会吃的一干二净 之后我就后悔
I'd eat all of it,
then I hate myself.
还有责怪我干嘛把他们带回家
And me for bringing it home
in the first place.
所以你就再也不买了
So did you stop buying it?
-是的 -因为你生气了
- Yeah, I did. - And you got so angry.
-哪有 -绝对有
- I was not angry. - A little bit angry.
他生气理所当然啊
Well, he should have been angry.
为什么她自控力差就要他也陪着受罪
Why should he be deprived because
she can't control herself?
因为她是他老婆 想帮助她
Because she's his wife and
he's trying to help her?
但是这真的对她好吗
Yeah, but is that really helping her?
当然
Yes!
为什么不让她自己学习自控呢
Not if we want her to
learn to control herself.
我们是指谁
"We?"
我只是认为这对他不公平
I just said it's not fair to him.
为什么每件事都要公平 你还当你是六岁小孩吗
Why does everything have to be fair?
What are you, six?
当然 和善点好吗
Of course... What? Let's keep it nice.
我忘了那天还有饼干呢
I just forget the cookies are there. So...
这就是为什么你适合彼得而我不适合了
That's why it's good you're
married to Peter and I'm not.
这是天意啊
That is absolutely the God's honest truth.
外面好冷
Ooh, it's cold out.
没人喜欢吃面包的
Nobody ate the bread, by the way.
你就吃啦
You did.
那是
Yeah, exactly.
是吗
Exactly?
问你个问题
Let me ask you a question.
别人问起我们为什么离婚 你怎么说的
When people asked why we got
divorced, what do you tell them?
我说我们不适合
I say I don't think you and I
should have been together.
弗兰呢 你跟她说我们的事了吗
What about Fran? I mean you tell her
everything, you talk to her about us.
看我多傻 她是你妻子 当然告诉了
Right. She's your wife. Right.
好吧
Yeah, okay.
刚才很高兴 对吧
That was fun, huh?
你五岁的时候开始织的这条毛毯
I started this blanket
when you were five years old.
我也不懂怎么选这个颜色了
I don't know what I was
thinking about this color.
我要把它打完 你就可以带着去上学了
I'm going to finish it,
so you can take it with you.
以防万一 我还是买一条吧
I'll probably buy another one, in case.
你在说什么 这条可以用的
What are you talking about?
This will be good.
你看这个干吗
Why are you looking at this?
不知道
I don't know.
我拿出来
I just pulled it out.
试着回忆我还记得的
I was trying to remember what I knew.
那时候我真的了解你爸了吗
Did I already know those
things about your dad?
那些我们经常争吵的东西
I mean the things we would fight about.
可能没有
Probably not.
我想我有
I think I did, actually.
我一直都知道
I think I always knew.
或者说感觉到了
Or felt them.
我只是没注意
I just wasn't paying attention.
但是我有你
But look at what I got, huh?
-我去睡觉了 -呆在这陪我啦
- I'm going to bed. - No, stay
here and cozy up with me.
我累了
I'm tired.
克洛伊 快点
Come on, Chloe.
这难吗
Is that hard?
不会啊 想学吗
Not at all. You want to learn?
想
Yeah.
我一直想教艾伦
I've been trying to teach
Ellen for the longest time!
是艾伯特
Albert.
你还和他老婆有来往吗
Are you still seeing his wife?
她肩膀痛 她也没有朋友
Well, she has a bad shoulder.
And she has no friends.
别用这种眼神看我
What? Don't look at me like that.
我搞砸了
I'm screwed up.
等一会
Hold on just one second.
我在处理一些破事
I'm in the middle of some bullshit.
-把你按摩椅放下吧 -好的 -然后我们再
- Can you just put your table down? - Sure.
-Then we will...
我马上好
I'll be right back.
慢慢来 别着急
Yeah. Take your time.
艾伯特 我们说好了的
We did, we agreed on it, Albert!
我在那 我记得非常清楚
Because I was there! I remember.
天哪 好吧 就这样
Oh, my God. Okay. Well, it is.
It's all worked out.
好 好 好 再见
Yes, it is. Okay, fine, good. Bye!
老天 什么时候才不用和他说话了
My God, I cannot wait till I don't
have to talk to him anymore.
发生什么了
What happened?
他想带泰斯去学校
He thinks he should take
Tess to school, not me.
泰斯想让我去 她就是这样说的
Tess wants it to be me, because she told me.
可是 谢谢 为什么不一起去
But, I mean... Thank you. Can't
you both just take her?
算了吧 我不想
I don't think so. No, I don't.
他非常不想她离开
He's such a wreck about her going away.
这样对她不好
She doesn't need that kind of energy right now.
她可以感受他在紧看着她
And he just focuses so much onto her.
She can feel it.
这不是件好事吗
Isn't that kind of nice, though?
我是说关心她
I mean, that he focuses?
或许他有个女朋友就会好点
Well, maybe if he had a girlfriend or
something so it would balance it out...
不过应该不可能
...but I don't see that happening.
为什么
Really? Why not?
因为他是屌丝
Because he's a loser.
哦哦
Uh-oh.
是很刻薄 不过形容他再适合不过了
Such a mean word, but it fits.
为什么
How does it fit?
比如说 这就是他的写照
For instance... this is typically Albert...
我们第一次出去的时候
...when we were first going out,
他床边什么都没有
he had nothing next to his bed.
连张桌子都没有
No table, nothing.
开始觉得很酷
At first I thought, "That's cute.
有点放荡不羁的感觉
It's kind of bohemian." Stuff like that.
我们结婚之后 我去买了
So then we got married and I went out
个非常可爱的床头柜
and bought these really
lovely bedside tables.
可是后来 他的东西
Then last year, I saw all of his stuff
又全部堆在床上
was on the side of the bed again.
我拿走了柜子
I mean, I took the tables, granted,
他就放肆了
but he never went out and replaced them.
把东西直接扔在地上
He's just content to just put
his shit on the floor again.
他就是不懂得生活
Metaphorically speaking, he's not
building a life for himself.
谁愿意和他在一起啊
I mean, who would date a person like that?
对
Right.
我不会接的
I'm not picking up.
玛丽安妮 接电话好吗
Marianne, please pick up the phone.
这事还没解决呢 我知道你听到了
We haven't resolved anything.
I know you're there.
不好意思 太囧了
This is so embarrassing. I'm sorry.
好吧 爱解决不解决
Fine. Don't deal with it.
这还是鸡毛蒜皮的小事
Okay, these are just little things.
最后 我们
Ultimately, we just...
他根本就不了解我
I never felt understood by him.
你知道吗
You know?
他不懂诗歌
He didn't get the poetry.
也不懂我
He never got me.
有人真正理解你吗
Has anyone ever gotten you?
我不知道
I don't know. I don't know.
那个肥男呢
What about the flabby guy?
他理解你吗
How's that?
可能吧
Yeah. Maybe.
double date. Or something like that。
我需要你 我们来个四人约会吧
I need you to meet him. We can do a
见一次面也不能看清他的真实面目啊
Not so you can decide what you think of him.
拜托啦 我都不知道该怎么了
Please? I'm losing all perspective here.
你自己搞定
Exactly! You don't need somebody else's!
你就不能答应我一次吗 求你了
Will you please just say yes
and do this for me? Please?
还有星星啊 太阳啊 月亮啊
They had stars and suns and moons.
我懂 我也讨厌那些
I know. I hate those.
为什么女人们都童心未泯呢
Tell me why do women like things that look
like they belong to children?
知道我喜欢什么吗 玩具屋家具 要是可以吃的话我就吃了
You know what I love? Dollhouse furniture.
I would eat it if I could.
有时候希望我还是单身 就可以用女生床单了
Sometimes I wish I was single, just
so I could have girlie sheets.
你一直都在想吧
You would love that.
我有花朵图案的床单
I have flowery sheets. They're not
all they're cracked up to be.
我喜欢你的床单
I like your flowery sheets.
别这样说啊
Oh! Don't sell me out, man.
如果有墨索里尼在上面就更好了
We're new. I'd like her sheets if
they had little Mussolinis on them.
你打算什么时候买床头柜
Talk to me when you get night tables.
他的床单很正常 不过没有床头柜
He has normal sheets, but no night tables.
我没有床头柜
So I don't have night tables.
他开玩笑呢
Maybe it's a metaphor.
或者是真的
Or maybe not!
我不知道
I don't know.
我做了很多妥协
I make a million compromises. It just seems...
不用花朵图案的床单也不是大事吧
...not having flowery
sheets is not a big deal.
我知道你做了很多牺牲
I know. I know you make compromises.
真的吗 看看他们
Really? What do you think they are?
别在这说
This is not the time.
有时候我就在想要是和一个
I'm just saying sometimes I wish
I was with somebody
对历史感兴趣的人在一起该有多好
who was more interested in history.
-什么 -历史
- What? - History.
好吧 我说说而已
Okay. I'm just saying.
-还要鳄梨沙拉吗 -我不要了
- More guacamole? - Not for me.
再给我来点
I'd love some, actually.
你知道鳄梨沙拉多少卡路里吗
You know how many calories
are in guacamole?
十吗
Ten.
别管他啊 他喜欢就让他吃嘛
Lay off the guy. He likes guacamole.
不要鳄梨沙拉了
You know what? We don't need the guac!
我吃芝士就好
I'll just stick with the cheese.
你知道我要送什么书给你吗 介绍卡路里的书
You know what I'm going to get you
as a present? A calorie book.
不要
Please don't.
这好像不太好吧
Yeah. A calorie book as
a gift is not so good.
伊娃说你是治疗师啊
Eva tells me you're a therapist.
跟我们说说最奇葩的病人
Tell us about your weirdest patient.
-这有损医德 -她不能说的
- No, I can't. - She can't.
不要说名字不就行了吗
Of course you can! You don't
have to name names, mate.
你还真是恪守原则啊
You're so uptight about confidentiality.
难道不应该吗
Shouldn't she be?
我的意思是
Well, you know. I mean.
好吧 有个病人挖鼻屎再吃下去
Okay. I have one patient who
picks his nose and eats it.
天哪
Oh, man!
-在你面前 -是的
- In front of you? - Yes.
他是小孩吗
Is he a child?
不会是你编的吧
Are you making this up?
真的是太恶心了
It is so gross and distracting.
他以为我不知道 不过怎么可能
He does it in this way he thinks I
can't see, but it's so obvious.
我不说是谁 不过是个名人
I won't say who it is, but he is famous.
-很有名 -不会吧
- Really famous. - He is not!
-我知道是谁 -你确定
- I know who it is. - You do?
-你不知道 -我肯定知道
- No, you don't. - I absolutely do.
莎拉 求求你告诉我们
Please, Sarah, tell us! Please!
好了 八卦到此为止
Okay! That's it! Show's over!
我喜欢喝醉的感觉 我绝对被高估了
I like being drunk. I really think
it's do think it's highly overrated.
不对 低估了我的酒量
Underrated!
你太大声了
You're shouting.
有吗 没有啊
I am? No, I'm not.
有一点点大声
You are. A little.
不好意思
Okay, I'm sorry.
我不想吵到别人
I don't want to wake up the small people.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你知道什么才好笑吗
You want to know something funny?
他不会轻声说话
This one here can't whisper.
什么
What?
你现在做给他们看啊
Will you do it right now?
Will you show them?
我在轻声说话
I'm whispering.
他会啊
That was a whisper.
什么 那才不是
Huh? What? No, it's not.
我这是吗
Can I?
你可以
Yeah, that was a whisper.
我呢
What about me?
你也可以
Yes, you can whisper.
这次呢
This is whispering.
不 你根本就不能
No, it's not. That is not a whisper at all.
-你在找他茬 -我没有
- You're picking on him. - No, I'm not!
你就是
You are.
有一点
You kind of are.
好吧 抱歉 只是我从来没有遇到过
Okay, I'm sorry. I've just,
never in my entire life...
一个人不会轻声说话的
...have I met anybody who
couldn't whisper at all.
好吧
Whatever.
不 你不要再发牢骚了
No. You are not allowed to
complain about her anymore.
凯茜 你在柜子里放什么了
Cathy? Did you put this in the drawer?
-是你放的吗 -不是
- Did you put this in the drawer? - No.
应该是小孩子放的
Maybe one of the kids did.
非常有可能哦
That actually could be this time.
但是我认为是你放的 因为我一直都能在
But I think you put it there, 'cause I find
柜子里找到这些奇怪的东西
weird stuff in these drawers all the time.
我尽力了
I clean the best I can.
我只想知道她是怎么想的
I'm just trying to understand
the thought process.
你说桌面上不要放东西
You like the counters clean.
可是不是叫你乱放啊
Yeah, but not by shoving weird
shit in the wrong drawers.
这垒球应该放在厨房吗 你这是帮倒忙
Does the ball belong in the kitchen?
How does that help me?
够了 我们
That's enough. I think we...
莎拉女士
You know what, Mrs. Sarah?
你的东西乱扔
I find your crap everywhere.
我哪里知道该放哪去啊
You think I know where to put it?
房间里全是你的东西
You leave stuff all over the house.
小孩子在墙上画画
You let your children write on the walls.
你用完的牙线就直接扔那
You floss your teeth and leave it.
老子不干了
You clean your own house.
你让我恶心 威尔先生 你不错
You people disgust me. But you was nice, Mr. Will.
谢谢 凯茜
Thanks, Cathy!
根本不用闹这么僵的
Really would have been kinder to fire her.
天哪
Oh, my God.
也许这时候说这个不对
Guys, my timing
maybe be a little off...
我觉得我会把球放柜子里
...but I think I put
the ball on the drawer.
这不好笑
Not funny.
别开玩笑了
Are you serious?
糟糕的一晚上 对吗
That wasn't a very fun evening, was it?
天哪
God! Yikes!
为什么你抓住我的缺点不放
Why do you care if I don't
know how to whisper?
这是干吗啊
What was that?
这很尴尬啊
I mean, that was embarrassing.
我只是拿你开涮而已 没有恶意
I was just joking around.
That was complete... nothing.
一本卡路里的书
A calorie book?
你准备送我一本卡路里的书
You're going to buy me a calorie book?
抱歉
Okay, well, I'm sorry.
肯定不会送你啦
I'm obviously not gonna
buy you a calorie book.
我还以为你真的喜欢我呢
I thought you actually liked me.
我是喜欢你啊
I do like you.
为什么我感觉你今晚我前妻附身一样
Why do I feel like I just spent
the evening with my ex-wife?
你干吗 送我回家
Wait, what are you doing,
driving me home?
对啊
Mmm-hmm.
哦
Oh.
在我家住吗
Are you going to spend the night?
不 以后吧
No. Not tonight.
好
Okay.
好啊
Hi.
艾伦和朋友出去了 我不想回家 可以在你家睡觉吗
Ellen went out with friends, but I didn't
really want to go home. Is this okay?
有你在真好
I'm glad you're here, actually.
在你家我总是很安心
I'm always so much more
comfortable at your house.
你可以
You know...
艾伦走了你可以住她房间啊
...you would be so welcome to stay
in Ellen's room once she's gone.
你想回家就可以回去 反正房间没人住
You'd have to check with your
mom, but the room will be empty.
-真的吗 -对啊
- Really? - Oh, yeah.
太棒了 谢谢
That would be awesome.
Thank you so much.
没关系
Sure.
谢谢
Thank you.
克洛伊 可以把我妈还给我了吗
Excuse me, Chloe,
but can I have my mom back?
宝贝 我们刚在看电影 就睡着了
Honey, we were just watching
something and we were just passed out.
下一步你是不是准备我走了让她住进来
Next you'll be asking her to
move into my room when I'm gone.
对不起
I'm sorry.
不 不关你事
No, it's not your fault, sweetie.
我还是回家吧
I better go home.
宝贝
Honey.
克洛伊需要人爱
Chloe is needy.
那我呢
Who's needy?
你知道我想
You know, I guess I am...
有点独立的生活
...just trying to feel
a little bit more separate.
也在适应中
Sort of prepare.
不过 我却只感到孤单 焦虑
But instead, I just feel
lonely and anxious and...
克洛伊又一直出现在家
...Chloe is always here.
对不起
I'm so sorry about that.
艾伦 你才是我的孩子啊
But, Ellen, you know you're my baby.
对吧 抱我一个 过来坐坐好吗
Right, honey? Give Mommy a hug.
Will you come sit with me?
给我看看弗兰和爸爸给了你什么
Can I see what Daddy and Fran got for you?
我还是去织毛毯吧
I'm going to finish my blanket.
还给了你什么
They get you anything else?
很好 也不占空间 非常有用
Oh, those are good. They don't
take up room. You'll use those.
你看了我的书吗
Hey, did you ever get a
chance to look at my book?
-我看了 -真的吗
- Oh, I did! - You did?
你的诗太美了
Yes. Your poems are beautiful!
我看不懂 不过我很喜欢
I mean, not that I understand
them, but I like them.
谢谢 你可以看懂的
Thank you. And I'm sure you understand them.
妈妈
Mom!
我们在外面
We're out here!
爸爸在车上 我忘拿手机了
Dad's in the car. I forgot my phone.
你们还没见面呢
Good, because I finally get
to introduce you guys.
这是伊娃
This is Eva.
泰斯
Tess!
你好
Hi?
你们认识吗
You guys know each other?
对啊
Uh, yeah, we know each other.
这是泰斯
This is Tess.
妈 她和爸爸在一起
Mom, she's dating Dad.
-什么 -你不知道吗
- What? - You didn't know that?
你和艾伯特在一起
You date Albert?
我糊涂了 等会
I'm not sure what's going on right now.
Wait a minute.
玛丽安妮
Hello! Marianne!
打扰了 泰斯 我们得出发了
Sorry to interrupt, but, Tess,
we really have to get going.
你好
Hi!
好啊
Hi.
你在这干吗
I don't understand. What are you doing here?
她给我按摩啊 我们是朋友
She massages me. We're friends.
我以为
I thought.
你是玛丽安妮的朋友
You're friends with Marianne.
我在派对上见到你
I met you...
你给我了名片
...at a party and you gave me your card...
错了 是我给了你名片
No, no. I gave you my card.
对 我们都参加了那个派对
Yes. I think you were at that same party.
我记起来了
Yeah, I remember the party.
我们两个你都见过
And you met us both.
所以你现在给她按摩 是吗
So what now you're her masseuse?
对
Yeah!
多久了
For how long?
那天派对后就开始了
Ever since we all met.
我并不知道
Well, I didn't know...
你和她是谁
...who she was, or who you... are, were.
所以
So...
后来你知道了 对吧
...you put it together at some point, right?
没有
No.
确定
No?
对不起 后来我是知道了
I'm sorry, at some point, I, um...
什么时候知道的
When?
大概
Well, I think...
什么时候
What? When?
When? Umm...
好吧
Yeah.
-泰斯 拿到手机没 -嗯
- Tess, You got your phone? - Yeah.
那我们走吧
Okay, why don't we go.
不好意思
I'm so sorry.
你没事吧 我来的不是时候吗
Are you okay? Should I not be here?
是的
Probably not.
-这次闯大祸了 -怎么了
- Oh, I screwed up big time. - What happened?
操蛋啊
Oh, shit!
我妈来了
Oh, that's my mom.
妈
Hi, Mom.
你没有女儿吧 她是我女儿
I'm sorry, do you have a daughter?
'Cause this one's mine.
-什么啊 -你以为你是谁啊 告诉我女儿
-What - Who do you think you are, telling her
需不需要和她男朋友做爱
she should have sex with her boyfriend?
她需要的是
You know what? What she needs to do is...
你住嘴
No, you shut it!
Dyke.
还没和你说厨房改造的事情
I didn't tell you about the kitchen remodel.
他们和罗马人谈石灰华
They talked to the guys in
Rome about the travertine.
不过他们拿起来的时候断了 我就直接走了
Apparently when they were lifting it up,
it snapped or something so I'm leaving without...
你爸在吗
Is your dad here?
他去市场了
He went to the market.
不好意思 这样冒昧的就来了
Sorry to just come over like this,
他没有回我电话 所以
but he hasn't been returning my calls, so...
我会告诉他你来过的
I'll tell him you came by.
你一个人吃的完吗
What are you gonna do with that?
你要吗
You want one?
好
Oh, sure.
Hi.
你知道这块面包多少卡路里吗
You know how many calories are in that?
我们谈谈吧
I just want to talk.
真的是个巧合
It really was a coincidence. Okay?
我想告诉你们来着
And I wanted it to stop.
但是她想要按摩 我们
But she needed massages and we sort of...
Oh, thank you.
我们成为了朋友
We sort of became friends...
我也慌了
...and I didn't know what to do.
她需要按摩吗
She needed massages?
你知道该怎么做 你只是不想而已
You knew what to do. You just didn't do it.
我很痛苦
Well, I was very torn.
你很痛苦
So while you were being torn...
她在离间我们
...she was poisoning our relationship
说我的坏话
and poisoning your perception of me.
为什么这么做
Why would you want that?
我不知道
I don't know.
我想说
I mean...
我可能在保护自己
Except maybe I was trying to protect
myself, you know, because...
你知道的
...you know...
我们都结过婚
...because we'd both been
married before, and...
不了解清楚对方的后果是什么我们都清楚
...you know how things can turn out.
那我们呢
What about us? What about...
你有保护我们吗
...protecting us?
我没有
I didn't protect us.
艾伯特 她说的坏话对我没影响
And it didn't get poisoned, Albert.
我还是很爱你
I still really wanted us
to keep seeing each other.
别为难我
I wouldn't know how, you know?
我很抱歉
I'm so, so, so sorry.
这听起来
I know this sounds...
很俗
...corny...
不过你确实伤了我的心
...but you broke my heart.
我已经不再年轻了
And I'm too old for that shit.
最糟糕的是
And the worst part...
最糟糕的是你让我
...the worst part of
it is that you made me
女儿怎么看我
look like an idiot in
front of my daughter.
我才是傻瓜
I'm the idiot!
我才是
I'm the idiot.
我很忙
Look, I got a lot to do.
泰斯学校的一些事情
Tess and everything. School
她什么时候走
When is she leaving?
下星期 她学校开学早
Next week. School starts early for her.
艾伦也是
Yeah, same for Ellen.
该与兴趣相依为命了
I guess we have to
get those hobbies going.
是啊
Guess so.
拜拜
Bye.
他很爱很爱你
He just really, really liked you.
我也是
I just really, really liked him.
Computer, What's the point in this?
You do all the thinking where we...
Just digging shelters in the snow
Build a house of dream and domino
I know it's fallen down
Got my headphones on
and I won't hear a sound
No, it's all broke down
Eyes out on the road
but no one comes along
When you want them to
Let your hair hang long
Yeah, that old north
wind is blowing
你怎么知道你的宿舍在哪
How will you gonna know which one is your room? Honey.
可以看到的 我们上次去的时候
It's all written down. And remember, Mom,
不是看到了吗
we saw everything on our visit.
我忘了
I don't remember anything.
-我没有啦 -好
- I do. - Ok.
她可以的
She's going to be great.
你可以的
You're going to be great.
我爱你们
I love you guys.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
Computer, what's the point in this?
You do all the thinking where we...
Just building shelters in the snow
Build a house of dream and domino
I know it's fallen down
Got my headphones on
and I won't hear a sound
Yeah, it's all broke down
Eyes out on the road
but no one comes along
When you want them to
我们的好女儿啊
Well, we made a fine person.
伊娃
Hey, Eva!
能帮我下吗
Do you think you can help me?
当然 天哪
Of course! Oh, my God.
我太傻了 对不起
I'm such an idiot! I'm sorry.
抱歉 那是 天哪
Sorry. Is that... Jeez.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
好重啊
This thing's heavy.
感恩节我们都去我妈家过
We always go to my mother's
house for Thanksgiving...
我兄弟姐妹疯在一起
...and I get in a fight
with my sister and brother.
我妹是第二胎 她问题多着呢
My sister's a middle child,
so she has issues.
你会怎么过
Anyway, what are you doing?
你假期怎么过的
Huh? What are you doing
for the holiday?
我去朋友家
I'm going to my friend's house.
人不多 不过
It's going to be a small group, but...
很好啊
That sounds nice.
呵呵
Oh, yeah.
你好
Hi, honey.
谢谢
Oh, thank you so much.
不用谢
No problem.
太香了吧
It really smells good in here!
我味觉失灵了
Yeah? I can't smell it anymore.
绝顶美味啊
It's unbelievably delicious sound...
Sounding. Smelling.
兴奋吗
You excited?
天哪 无比兴奋
Oh, my God, beyond!
你觉得她变样了吗
You think she'll look different?
可能长胡子了
Yeah, maybe she grew
a beard or something.
你知道莎拉·劳伦斯学院的
You know how it is at Sarah Lawrence.
我昨天和她视频了
No, she looks the same.
I Skyped with her yesterday.
她应该变胖了
Actually, I think she's gained weight.
什么时候去接她
What time are you picking her up?
两点
Not till two.
五点开饭 你应该直接从这
We're eating at five... you should just
出发去机场
come straight here from the airport.
用高档盘子吧
Oh, let's use the fancy plates.
你不是不喜欢吗
But you say you don't like them.
今天是感恩节
I know. But it's Thanksgiving...
就应该用我不喜欢的盘子
you're supposed to use the ugly plates.
待会见 拜拜
Okay, I'll see you. Bye.
-拜拜 伊娃 -拜拜 凯茜
- Bye, Eva! - Bye, Cathy.
你好
Hi.
嗯
Oh, wow.
好吧
Okay.
我很少这样干
I don't always park in front of your house.
我以前直接开过去的
I usually just drive by.
有时候我也会开车经过你家
Sometimes I drive by your house, too.
是吗
You do?
你看起来不错啊
You look good.
你也是
You, too.
谢谢
Thank you.
泰斯回来过感恩节吗
Is Tess coming home for Thanksgiving?
她已经回来了 她去她妈那了
She's already here. She's over at her mother's.
我晚点过去
I'm going over there later.
你想来吗
You want to come?
艾伦
And Ellen is...
艾伦今天下午回来
This afternoon. She's coming home this afternoon.
没有她还习惯吗
You been okay without her?
嗯
Oh, sure, yeah.
I mean, she's not going back.
'Cause I've built a cage.
好主意
What a good idea!
我想你
I've missed you.
我也想你
I missed you, too.
我买了床头柜
Oh, I should tell you...
I bought some night tables.
真的吗
You did?
肯定是假的啊
No.
我没有买啦
No, I didn't.
无所谓啦
Okay. That's good.
I like your toothy smile
It never fails to beguile
Whichever way
the wind is blowing
I like the way this is going
I like to watch TV with you
There's really nothing
That I would rather do
Then maybe we can go to bed
And get up
and do it all again
I like the way your pants fit
And how you stand
and how you sit
Whatever seeds
that you're sowing
I like the way this is going
I don't care about the past
None of it was made to last
It's not who you've known
But who you're knowing
I like the way this is going